Yanuo Deng (James)

1565 Cress Way, Olivehurst, CA, 95961 * (408)444-5520 * deng.ya.nuo@gmail.com * Cantonese

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Focused professional with 15+ years of experience and a proven knowledge of embedded system(linux/RTOS), and digital & analogy circuit design. Aming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the Integrated Circuit Engineer, Software Engineer, or Network Security Engineer role at your company.

EXPERIENCE

C-MATRIXTECH CO.LTD., Zhuhai, Guangdong, 3 person R&D/6

Integrated Circuit Designer, Dec 2017 - Feb 2019

- * Verilog coding, FPGA simulation and debug for self-powered SOC chip.
- * MCU debug; Port C-language from Assembly for the MCU; Analog circuit design.
- * Achieved self-powered MCU SOC used on iPhone data cables; Mass production 10 per month.

VIOMI CO.LTD., Foshan, Guangdong, 3 person R&D/200

Software (Firmware) Engineer, May 2017 - Oct 2017

- * Linux driver for the wifi chip; Speech Recognition App for Linux.
- * Achieved smart wireless Speech Recognition module ; Mass production 3k per month.

BLUEWAY CO.LTD., Huizhou, Guangdong, 5 person R&D/2500

Software (Firmware) Engineer, May 2016 - Apr 2017

* FreeRTOS system migration for the embedded board, target for electric mowers.

ADON CO.LTD., Foshan, Guangdong, 3 person R&D/350

Software (Firmware) Engineer, Oct 2013 - Dec 2015

* Linux driver & app for the Homepod (wifi speaker/charger for iPhone); Mass production, 3k per month.

SKYIT SOFTWARE CO.LTD., Shunde, Guangdong, 5 person R&D/500

Software Engineer, Dec 2011 - Jul 2013

* Windows Client App by C#; Data API by C for the first order a meal App in China

VBRIDGE MICROSYSTEM INC, San Jose, CA, 5 person R&D/12

Digital Integrated Circuit Engineer, Apr 2005 - May 2008

- * AES, DES, 3DES, MD5, SHA1, CRC : ipcores for the security engineer.
- * 5 bit MCU for the dual-MIPS SOC chip
- * All IP cores include specification, testbench, RTL; All IP cores verified by the SOC Chip

EDUCATION

XI'AN university of technology, Xi'an city, Shannxi, China

Master of Science (M.S.) Microelectronics & Solidstate Electronics (Apr 2005)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- * C, Verilog, Vim, Bash, Perl, Go-language, Gnumake, git
- * Linux / FreeRTOS driver

Certifications

Electronics Engineer Certification, Foshan city, Aug 2008